Rina Yuki of Bucca won the championship!
Rina Yuki won the Beach Flags!
Now, here is the second event!
The Shuttle Run from Hell!
Here is the second event.
I prefer long distance,
I will do my best!
Anyway, I will do my best.
No strategy, just go for it.
I'll give it my all!
I will make up for it!
I will do my best!
To be honest, everyone is strong,
I'm going to give it my all.
I am not so confident in long distance,
But I've trained hard,
I will win with my mind!
Next time, I want to win first place for sure,
Next time, I want to make sure to get the first place,
There is a next time!
I think it's a competition that I have to win at all.
I want to get the first place by Dantotsu already!
I'm going to do my best.
I've been practicing, so now I'm going to do my best
I won't give up.
Even if I don't get first place
I'm going to slip up and get into a good position.
I think it's going to be tough if you give it your all. The one who keeps his own pace while watching the pace of others will win.
I think it's all about the dash at the end.
I don't think it's right to let idols do this.
I wonder if they'll be able to keep up the pace.
Now, please cheer for the audience!
Now for the second event, the shuttle run from hell!
Number 1, the cart.
Here we go.
First one, we're going to go pretty fast.
The last one to go is going to be eliminated.
Who's the last one standing?
Nine. Twelve. Is that dangerous?
How's it looking?
Number 12 is out.
Number 12, Hina HIMENO's move... has been eliminated.
Unfortunately, she's eliminated.
The second round will begin immediately after the interval.
I'm so disappointed.
The second round will begin immediately.
Good luck, Rei!
Good luck, Ray!
The second round will begin immediately after the interval.
There are 11 of us left.
They've considerably increased their speed from the first race.
Riko Iwamoto, number 11, is helping out quite a bit.
There are two behind her.
While recovering a little strength.
Race 2 is about to begin.
about to begin.
Good, good, good.
Nine out.
Not-so-commie, Sumana Magee has unfortunately been eliminated from the race.
He's slipping.
10 out
Thank goodness I didn't fall.
I'd like to hug you right now.
Are you okay?
There's only 10 of us left.
Come on!
You guys are faster than I thought you'd be.
From the start.
Ten out.
Out 10.
Number 10 out.
Number 10 out
We're off to a good start.
Third game in a row, almost side by side.
How's that?
One down here.
Aaaaah!
Six, seven, look out!
Number 7 out.
Number seven is Kanami Tsujino, the super-triggering publicity department.
Aaaaah!
It's okay, I did my best, I did my best.
I did my best.
Yes!
Cross is in.
KW's hard work
KW's effort
Good luck to KW!
Ten out.
There are 10 players left.
Out 10.
10 out
is so hard!
I want to quit.
Race four is about to start.
Yes, sir.
I'm gradually getting out of breath.
Speed is also required.
Here we go.
Sweet Steady, is Shiraishi okay?
Shiraishi's a little behind.
Shiraishi wants to go faster.
Number 6 out.
Sweet Steady, Mayumi Shiraishi.
She's out.
So close, so close, so close.
She did her best.
Her face is cute, so it's OK.
They're all fast.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No good.
I'm sorry, but...
I can't win.
We've got to do something to make up for this.
Game over.
I'm up to speed. - I'm up to speed. - I'm up to speed.
Speed up! Speed up!
Speed up.
This is the part where you don't want to drop out.
This is the fifth run.
Here we go.
They're lining up.
How's your stamina?
Masai, are you okay?
Masai?
Manaca?
Number two out.
AKB48
Masai Mayu, you're eliminated here.
Oh, no.
Masai has been eliminated here.
You've worked so hard, haven't you?
You did your best.
Good boy, good boy.
I don't want to do this for the rest of my life
Speed up.
What?
He sped up.
This is really bad.
I sped up.
You guys were fast.
You were fast.
You're crazy, you're not human.
They're not human.
Sixth run.
We're off.
We've started.
We're off to a good start.
MGT48 Sage Radar.
A little slow, huh?
He's slipping.
Sage?
Manaka?
How's it looking?
Number four out.
MGT48 Sage Radar
Seventh place confirmed.
He's eliminated here.
MGT48 Sage Rader.
That was so close.
Oh, my God.
How did they all go so fast?
Oh!
That's great.
That was close.
Six pots.
2 pots
Highly rated
Can't stay still
only
Top Dry
There's still some rocks and birds left!
We're off to a good start.
Manacamana on 10.
Fruit zipper!
Can he catch up?
Manaca, go for it!
Manaka and Tomo first.
Fruit zipper
Manaka Manaka
She's eliminated here.
I could see it on your face.
This is
I'm sorry to hear that.
but pretty much in front of my momo.
I've defeated myself, haven't I?
We'll drop out one by one from here.
There are only five of us left
An epic survival race
has begun.
The remaining five.
What do you think?
Who will survive?
Uh-oh.
Push.
Tangled legs or slipped...?
Oops.
2nd place, Fukumatsu Women's Prize
Mizuki Miyagi Daihaku
Unfortunately eliminated here
With a big win
Oops!
I'm so tired.
I think my legs
I got a cramp in my leg.
You've already worked so hard!
Drink lots of water and take in oxygen.
Oops...
Oops!
One down.
Which leaves us with the top three.
Ooh...
Here we go!
Almost a full-speed dash
Ah, Iwamoto.
Yay!
Full speed dash!
And Iwamoto!
He's chasing us out here!
How's it going?
Oops!
Full speed dash!
Iwamoto, how's it going?
He's catching up here.
How's it going?
Number 3 out!
Miki Ito out!
Full Mousson, 4 hours, 29 minutes.
SK48 Miki Ito
We lost here.
You can't let them take it.
She hates to lose.
I'm so disappointed.
Two more steps.
How many steps?
The only one left is...
Rina Yuki of Ukka
Kazamino Nomo from Ebichu.
Riko Iwamoto of Oku-Ao.
Hot Honda.
I can do it!
I can do it! I can do it!
Show us your instant, Kazami!
Iwamoto's still here.
Yuki's
With his KODKO speed...
I couldn't cover it
YUJIRI Ryo ücken
Monday
dropped out
Now that I've put in the last
I'm looking forward to the next one!
Oshigami 2 people
B BENEä
DENNERY
SK48 SHICHI Tsubasa
YEAS FAN
The team of mindfulness about 2
Kazami, 16, and Iwamoto, 16.
Now the finals!
Nora-kun, Nora-kun, Nora-kun
Oh man, I'm watching Major League Baseball, I'm watching Major League Baseball.
I'm looking at the 16-year-old, the 17-year-old.
Who will win?
The last race.
It's started.
Yuya Iwamoto leads.
Just a few people, speed at the end.
It's Iwamoto, it's Iwamoto!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, well, that's great
ah?
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ahh!
The winner is the blue sky I wanted to see
Riko Iwamoto
Ahh!
It's started
Yuya Iwamoto in the lead?
Just a few people, speed at the end
It's Iwamoto, it's Iwamoto
blue sky
ал Miss.
Miss.
Here we are.
Yes, ma'am.
This is
Tatsuo Iwamoto
Ten minutes.
That's great!
Also, Towa and the other members' support for Rico to do his best was very encouraging.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Seiki, yes, great.
Well, you know, when Mr. Iwamoto was turning, it looked like he was slipping.
So, I was watching him with fear, wondering when he would fall down there, but he kept his speed until the end.
I was very impressed.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Mr. Oshima, everyone was so cool!
You were really cool.
And the idols were so cute and cool.
I don't know what it was, but you were looking at me.
I was almost in tears!
Satoko Iwamoto won the first place!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
You were really fast, Riko!
But I also had a lot of fun doing shift browns.
I will definitely say "1st place" next time!
You did a great job, you did a great job, you did a great job.
Nice idol!
The first place winner was Satoko Iwamoto of 6Ao
The second runner-up was Nobuko Kazami, Ebichu!
She is really cool.
She is a girl who usually gives her all and does her best in everything she does.
I think her perseverance and hard-working spirit came out in her.
She was so cool!
She's full of frustration.
I want to do it again next time.
I want to do it.
Shuttle run at the matchmaking place.
That's cool.
It's okay, just take a drag.
I'm still working on it.
I just feel like I'm not as young as I used to be.
That's what I'm trying to say the most, that I'm not as young as I should be.
That's what I thought.
I want you to trick your sister out of her.
I'll do my best to show that I'm an adult.
I wanted her to show me that she's got room to grow up.
We're in a good position and on a good pace.
I'm hoping that we can continue to get more and more first places.
I hope that she will continue to get more and more first places and eventually win the championship.
As I thought, the girls with strong legs and interest won the competition.
Thank you very much.
The results are good for those who don't train on a regular basis.
It was great.
Who will win and go to the main SASUKE competition?
I'm looking at it from the perspective of SASUKE.
Thank you for watching!
invincible
Surprising.
I'd cry if I did this snake.
I thought about it with my trainer until the last minute.
More to come! Subscribe to our channel!